♪ 'Twas brillig, and the slithy toves ♪
♪ Did gyre and gimble in the wabe; ♪
♪ All mimsy were the borogoves, ♪
♪ And the mome raths outgrabe. ♪
♪ Beware the Jabberwock, my son! ♪
♪ The jaws that bite, the claws that catch! ♪
♪ Beware the Jubjub bird, and shun ♪
♪ The frumious Bandersnatch! ♪
♪ He took his vorpal sword in hand: ♪
♪ Long time the manxome foe he sought— ♪
♪ So rested he by the Tumtum tree, ♪
♪ And stood awhile in thought. ♪
♪ And as in uffish thought he stood, ♪
♪ The Jabberwock, with eyes of flame, ♪
♪ Came whiffling through the tulgey wood, ♪
♪ And burbled as it came! ♪
♪ One, two! One, two! And through and through ♪
♪ The vorpal blade went snicker-snack! ♪
♪ He left it dead, and with its head ♪
♪ He went galumphing back. ♪